翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
Now, we stripped away all this functionality, right?
现在我们删除了所有功能对吗？
We took away all the things that IntNode could do.
拿走了 IntNode 可以做的所有事情
So we're going to put it back next.
接下来要把它放回去
And we're going to do it by adding a couple of simple methods first.
我们将通过添加几个简单的方法来实现
They'll be called addFirst and getFirst.
它们称为 addFirst 和 getFirst
So let's jump right in.
直奔主题吧
And you're welcome to pause the video and ponder how you might do this.
欢迎暂停视频，思考如何做到这一点
When I watch lectures, I do that, right?
我观看讲座时会这样做
When someone's about to code something,
有人要编写代码
I try and anticipate their next moves,
我试着预测他们的行动
or if I'm watching a math lecture, especially--
尤其是看数学讲座时
because then I feel like I can better appreciate the thing the teacher's about to do.
因为那样我就能更好地欣赏老师接下来做的事情
So in this case, I'm going to have public void addFirst.
在本例中，我将使用 public void addFirst
And what does this method do?
这个方法是做什么的呢？
Adds-- oh, it should have been a parameter--
这应该有一个参数
adds x to the front of the list.
将 x 添加到 List 的前面
How should that work?
那该怎么做呢？
Well, first, presumably, it should be a reference to the front of the list.
首先，它应该是对 List 前面的引用
So what I really ought to do is say something like--
我应该做的是...
well, maybe I'll look to IntNode or my IntList class for inspiration.
也许我会从 IntNode 或 IntList 类中寻找灵感
That might be the easiest way. I'm lazy.
这可能是最简单的办法了，我很懒
I don't want it to do any thinking.
不想做任何思考
Ah, here we go.
在这里
This is what I wanted.
这就是我想要的
So when we added to the front of an int list before,
在 List 前面添加元素
we had something like this.
我们有过类似的东西
So looking at the same pattern,
方式是一样的
I can basically say, OK, the first pointer
基本上，first 指针
should really just be a new, in this case, IntNode.
在本例中，应该 new IntNode()
I'm going to put in-- oops-- x and first.
然后放入 x 和 first
And that piece of code is just like what we did before.
这段代码和之前做的一样
Now, if you didn't quite understand the sleight of hand I did to build this method,
可能你不太理解我构造这个方法的做法
if you don't quite get what this line of code is actually saying,
或者没有完全理解这行代码的实际含义
well, the previous lecture, we spent a little more time with it.
上一节课我们花了很多时间
I'm not going to go through it in great detail again.
我不打算再详细地讲一遍了
But remember, you can always put this code through the visualizer and see what's going on.
但你始终可以将此代码放入 visualizer 中，看看发生了什么
I could, but I won't because in the previous lecture.
我不会做一遍了，因为之前做过了
But you can break this up into multiple lines.
你可以把它分成多行
And that's an exercise you might do in order to help understand it.
这是一个帮助你理解的练习
So that's what addFirst should look like.
这就是 addFirst 方法
What about getFirst?
getFirst 呢？
That one will actually be a little easier.
这个实际上会简单一点
So this one returns the first item in the list.
它返回 List 中的第一项
And so in this case, that's pretty straightforward.
这种情况下，这是相当简单的
All we need to do is say whatever the first reference goes to, whatever IntNode that is, we'll just return that IntNode's item.
无论 first 指向什么，只需返回 IntNode 的 item
And this right here gives us out SLList.
这就为我们从 SLList 取出来了
So suppose we wanted to make a list of the numbers--
假设我们要制作数字 List
still have a main?
有 main 吗？
Yes.
有
I'll move it down.
移到下面去
So let's suppose we wanted to--
假设我们想要...
sorry about all the scrolling--
抱歉鼠标滚动了
get you situated. All right.
好了
So here's my class.
这是我的类
There's my constructor-- addFirst, getFirst.
这是我的构造函数，还有 addFirst 和 getFirst
So main-- when we want to make a list of, say, the numbers 5, 10, 15, it might look something like this--
当想要制作一个 List 时，比方说数字5、10、15，它可能看起来像这样
L dot addFirst 10, L dot addFirst 5.
L.addFirst(10)，L.addFirst(5)
And now if I print getFirst, hopefully I should get back 5.
现在打印 getFirst 希望得到5
So I run this.
运行
And I get 5.
得到5
Great.
太棒了
So let's compare what we did in this context right here.
让我们来比较一下刚刚做了什么
This is SLList, right?
这是 SLList 对吗？
This is all the code we just wrote.
这就是刚刚写的所有代码
This is the IntNode class.
这是 IntNode 类
This is the example usage we just wrote.
这是刚刚编写的用法示例
Let's compare what we did with this clothed or non-naked recursive data structure with what we would have done before.
让我们将这个非裸露的递归数据结构与以前所做的进行比较
On the right, we see what it's like to use a naked recursive data structure.
右侧使用裸露的递归数据结构
You want to add something to the front?
想在 List 前面加点什么吗？
Well, L equals new IntList L, comma, 10.
那就要 L = new IntList(L, 10)
By contrast, with SLList, we say L dot addFirst and put in the number 10.
相比之下，SLList 只需 L.addFirst(10)
So hopefully, it's clear when you look at this,
希望你看到这个就明白了
this just reads easier, particularly if you're a novice.
这个易于阅读，特别是对新手来讲
Now, again, there are some programmers who prefer and enjoy programming that looks and feels like this.
再说一次，有些程序员更喜欢这种编程形式
And they're not wrong.
他们没有错
But the normal Java convention is something like what we see on the left.
但是正常的 Java 约定一般是左边这样
So a visual picture of this whole story--
整个过程图形化
on the top, we see the naked recursive data structure
顶部是裸露的递归数据结构
where, crucially, anytime we are working with a list,
最重要的是，处理 List 的时候
we have pointers directly into the raw stuff of the list.
我们有直接指向 List 中原始内容的指针
I may have one variable that points to the front of the list, another variable that--
我可能有一个变量指向 List 的前面，另一个变量...
My phone's ringing.
电话响了
Hello? Hi.
Hug：你好?
You're in a video on the internet forever.
Hug：你将永远出现在网络视频里
What?
Girl：什么？
Oh, I was recording a video for class.
Hug：我在录课堂视频
Oh.
Girl：哦
So I'll call you right back.
Hug：我马上给你回电话
To continue, the user of the IntList has pointers potentially directly into the naked recursive data structure,
我们继续，IntList 的用户具有指向裸露的递归数据结构的指针
which srequires them to understand recursion,
这需要他们理解递归
whereas the user of the SLList has a middleman to go through.
而 SLList 的用户通过中间人
So if you want the first item, you call getFirst.
如果想要第一项，调用 getFirst
And ideally, there's no way around this middleman.
理想情况下，没办法绕过这个中间人
翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）